00:00:06,407 - > 00:00:09,143
♪ MTV... ♪
音乐电视...♪
00:00:10,444 - > 00:00:11,778
Previously on Yellowstone...
《黄石公园》前情提要...
00:00:13,214 - > 00:00:15,691
Fished a radio collar
out of the Yellowstone
River.
从黄石河中捞出一个无线电项
圈。
4 4
00:00:15,715 - > 00:00:17,593
Seen any wolves around lately?
最近有看到狼吗？
00:00:17,617 - > 00:00:19,562
Sounds like poachers.
听起来像偷猎者。
00:00:19,586 - > 00:00:21,497
- Sure does.
- 确实如此。
- Care to ride with us?
- 介意和我们一起去吗？
00:00:21,521 - > 00:00:23,599
Monica wants to have a funeral.莫妮卡想举行葬礼。
00:00:23,623 - > 00:00:26,535
She wants him here
where she can
visit.
她想让他在这里，这样她
就可以去看他了。
00:00:26,559 - > 00:00:28,672
Whatever she wants,
you... You give it,
son.
不管她想要什么，你...你来
吧，儿子。
00:00:28,696 - > 00:00:30,739
I can't serve both.
我不能两者兼顾。
00:00:30,763 - > 00:00:33,076
I choose her
and I choose my
son.
我选择她，也选择我
的儿子。
00:00:33,100 - > 00:00:36,112
You promised and you took
millions in lease
payments!
你答应了而且你收了几百万的租
金！13
00:00:36,137 - > 00:00:37,146
You have no case.
你没有证据。
00:00:37,170 - > 00:00:38,814
And you know it.
你知道的。
00:00:38,838 - > 00:00:40,984
You're better than I expected.
你比我想象的要好。
00:00:41,008 - > 00:00:45,755
I am here just to
find a soft
landing.
我来这里只是为了寻找一
个软着陆。
00:00:45,779 - > 00:00:48,424
How busy are you tomorrow night?
你明天晚上有多忙？
00:00:48,448 - > 00:00:49,893
New York would
纽约会
like to drop the suit.
我想撤诉。
00:00:49,917 - > 00:00:53,896
Find a way to ruinthis family,
Ellis.
想办法毁掉这个家，埃利
斯。
00:00:53,920 - > 00:00:55,564
Hey, let's go to
a bar in Bozeman.
嘿，我们去波兹曼的酒
吧吧。
00:00:55,588 - > 00:00:58,167
Yeah, that's a
bad idea every
time.
是啊，每次都是坏主
意。
00:00:58,192 - > 00:01:00,103
Aren't you a
tall drink of
water?
你不是一大杯水吗？
00:01:00,128 - > 00:01:01,737
I'm married. Go on.
我结婚了。继续吧。
00:01:01,762 - > 00:01:03,231
I'm taking your husband home.
我要带你丈夫回家。25
00:01:20,347 - > 00:01:21,614
What day is it?
今天是星期几？
00:01:24,185 - > 00:01:25,585
Thursday, I think.
我想是星期四。
00:01:38,031 - > 00:01:39,533
What happened to you?
你怎么了？
00:01:41,067 - > 00:01:42,436
Fucking men.
该死的男人。
00:01:43,804 - > 00:01:46,382
Worked you over
pretty good,
huh?
把你折腾得够呛吧。
00:01:46,406 - > 00:01:49,009
I'm talking about
the cop that
arrested me.
我说的是逮捕我的警察。
00:01:52,945 - > 00:01:55,625
Prick is in the
club three nights aweek.
混蛋一周有三个晚上在俱
乐部。
00:01:55,649 - > 00:01:57,284
He can't cut me a break?
他不能放过我吗？
00:01:59,587 - > 00:02:01,188
They get you for D.U.I.?
他们抓到你酒后驾车了？
00:02:02,456 - > 00:02:03,790
Aggravated assault.
严重人身攻击。
00:02:05,793 - > 00:02:08,805
Some bitch from
California tried to fuck
my husband
一个来自加州的婊子想上我丈夫
00:02:08,829 - > 00:02:11,240
so I beat her
所以我打了她
with a beer
bottle. 37
00:02:11,264 - > 00:02:14,377
So, you're like
a fucking
criminal.
所以，你就像个该死的
罪犯。
00:02:14,401 - > 00:02:16,103
I am the wrath
of a woman
scorned.
我是一个被蔑视的女人
的愤怒。
00:02:16,204 - > 00:02:17,305
Call it what you will.
随你怎么称呼它。
00:02:18,806 - > 00:02:22,186
It's always some
总是有些
bitch from California.
来自加州的婊子。
00:02:22,210 - > 00:02:23,276
Every fucking time.
每次都是。
00:02:25,712 - > 00:02:27,814
Bethany Dutton. Let's go.
贝瑟尼·达顿。我们走吧。
00:02:29,817 - > 00:02:31,461You don't look like a Bethany.
你看起来不像贝瑟尼。
00:02:31,485 - > 00:02:34,997
I'm not a Bethany. I'm a Beth.
我不是贝瑟尼。我是贝丝。
00:02:47,534 - > 00:02:48,912
My hero.
我的英雄。
00:02:48,936 - > 00:02:50,371
Knock when you're done.
完事后敲门。
00:02:54,542 - > 00:02:58,222
Boy, you have really
fucking done it this
time.
伙计，你这次真的做到了。
00:02:58,246 - > 00:03:00,257
What's the big deal, Jamie?
有什么大不了的，杰米？
00:03:00,281 - > 00:03:02,891
I got into a bar
我进了一家酒吧fight in Bozeman.
在波兹曼战斗。
00:03:02,915 - > 00:03:04,728
I mean, Montana Board of Tourism
我是说，蒙大拿州旅游局
00:03:04,752 - > 00:03:06,462
should put that
应该把那个
on fucking t-shirts.
在他妈的 t 恤上。
00:03:06,486 - > 00:03:08,465
I don't think the
Montana Board of
Tourism
我不认为蒙大拿州旅游局
00:03:08,489 - > 00:03:10,766
is too fond of
locals beating the
shit
太喜欢本地人挨打了
00:03:10,790 - > 00:03:12,968
out of tourists on vacation.
度假的游客。
00:03:12,992 - > 00:03:14,837
Well, that's why I called you.
这就是我打电话给你的原因。56
00:03:14,861 - > 00:03:17,507
You can find the rug to
sweep this under,
right?
你能找到地毯来打扫，对吗？
00:03:17,531 - > 00:03:19,165
There is no rug
没有地毯
for this one, Beth.
为了这个，贝丝。
00:03:19,266 - > 00:03:20,909
It's a County Attorney issue.
这是县检察官的问题。
00:03:20,933 - > 00:03:23,812
So your best bet is to hope
this woman has a plane to
catch
所以你最好的办法就是希望这个女人能去
赶飞机
00:03:23,836 - > 00:03:25,981
or she's too
hungover to come
down here
或者她宿醉未醒不能来这里
00:03:26,006 - > 00:03:27,817
and file formal charges.
并提出正式指控。
00:03:27,841 - > 00:03:30,554
This is your legal advice?
这是你的法律建议吗？
00:03:30,578 - > 00:03:31,888
Sit here and hope?
坐在这里希望？
00:03:31,912 - > 00:03:37,060
It's not advice.
It's your only
option.
这不是建议。这是你唯一的
选择。
00:03:37,084 - > 00:03:38,795
If she doesn't file charges,
如果她不起诉，
00:03:38,819 - > 00:03:40,864
and that's a big fucking
"if" considering the
photo
考虑到照片，这是一个他妈的
大“如果”
00:03:40,888 - > 00:03:43,866
I saw of the
grapefruit on herforehead,
我看到她额头上的葡萄柚，
00:03:43,890 - > 00:03:46,269
then I will ask
the County
Attorney
那我会问县检察官
00:03:46,293 - > 00:03:49,305
to show some mercy based
以示仁慈
on your diminished capacity
因为你能力下降了
00:03:49,329 - > 00:03:51,299
to control your
fucking emotions.
控制你该死的情绪。
00:03:53,300 - > 00:03:58,038
So, yeah, you
just sit here and
hope.
所以，是的，你就坐在
这里希望。
00:04:01,074 - > 00:04:04,621
But no matter what, if
this reaches the
press,
但不管怎样，如果这事传到媒
体上，73
00:04:04,645 - > 00:04:05,621
it's a big
embarrassment for our
father.
这对我们的父亲来说是一个很大
的尴尬。
00:04:05,645 - > 00:04:06,979
You mean my father.
你是说我父亲。
00:04:08,515 - > 00:04:11,419
Your father's out of chances to
be embarrassed, isn't he,
Jamie?
你父亲没机会尴尬了，对吧，杰米？
00:04:12,853 - > 00:04:15,331
I'm going to go back to my cell.
我要回我的牢房了。
00:04:15,355 - > 00:04:17,401
I'm going to take a nap.
我要小睡一会儿。
00:04:17,425 - > 00:04:20,370
And you're going to sit on
你要坐在
the fucking steps of this place
这地方的台阶
00:04:20,394 - > 00:04:22,572
and you're going to
你会的
wait for Miss California
等待加州小姐
00:04:22,596 - > 00:04:27,143
to walk up, and when she
走上去，当她
does, you are going to stop her.
是的，你要阻止她。
00:04:27,167 - > 00:04:29,470
How the hell am
我到底怎么了
I going to do that?
我会那样做吗？
00:04:30,838 - > 00:04:32,473
It's not my problem, Jamie.
这不是我的问题，杰米。
00:06:09,437 - > 00:06:12,048
Hey. You got this
Dutton assault
case?
嘿。你接手了达顿袭击案
吗？
00:06:12,072 - > 00:06:13,716Uh, yes, sir.
呃，是的，先生。
00:06:13,740 - > 00:06:16,819
Why no charges
为什么不起诉
against the complainant?
针对投诉人？
00:06:16,843 - > 00:06:18,221
It was a bar fight, wasn't it?
那是一场酒吧斗殴，是吗？
00:06:18,245 - > 00:06:20,346
It was one hell of a
这是一个地狱
bar fight from the report.
报道中的酒吧斗殴。
00:06:20,447 - > 00:06:23,315
There is no self
defense in a bar
fight,
在酒吧打架是没有自卫的，
00:06:23,451 - > 00:06:25,411
which is to say the
victim is a defendant as
well.
也就是说受害者也是被告。
00:06:25,452 - > 00:06:26,696
Is she coming in?
她进来了吗？91
00:06:26,720 - > 00:06:29,966
- I'm waiting for her now.
- 我现在在等她。
- I'll wait with you.
- 我会和你一起等。
00:06:41,668 - > 00:06:45,247
You have the Montana
Educators Luncheon at
noon.
你中午有蒙大拿教育工作者午餐
会。
00:06:45,271 - > 00:06:47,283
Cancel it.
取消它。
00:06:47,307 - > 00:06:49,341
Governor, I think that
sends the wrong
message.
州长，我认为这传达了错误的信
息。
00:06:49,476 - > 00:06:53,856
All right, who exactly attends
the Montana Educators
Luncheon?
好吧，谁会参加蒙大拿教育家午餐会？96
00:06:53,880 - > 00:06:56,259
Everyone. Senator
Perry will be
there.
所有人。佩里参议员会去
的。
00:06:56,283 - > 00:06:58,060
Legislators, School
Superintendents,
立法者，学校管理者，
00:06:58,084 - > 00:06:59,528
the President of Montana State.
蒙大拿州的总统。
00:06:59,552 - > 00:07:01,387
Why do they call it
the Educators Euncheon
为什么他们称之为教育家恩施
00:07:01,488 - > 00:07:02,889
if there's no educators there?
如果那里没有教育者呢？
00:07:04,557 - > 00:07:08,004
It's Thursday, Clara, all
the educators are in
school.
今天是星期四，克拉拉，所有的老师
都在学校。
Tell you what, when
告诉你，什么时候
the Educators' Luncheon
教育家午餐会
00:07:09,797 - > 00:07:12,199
is about teachers, I'll go.
是关于老师的，我会去的。
00:07:20,540 - > 00:07:21,884
Who are they?
他们是谁？
00:07:21,908 - > 00:07:23,511
It's the policy
advisors' meeting.
这是政策顾问会议。
00:07:25,713 - > 00:07:27,413
Policy advisors for who?
谁的政策顾问？
00:07:28,848 - > 00:07:30,216
For you.
给你的。108
00:07:33,987 - > 00:07:35,598
How can my policy
advisors have a
meeting
我的政策顾问如何开会
00:07:35,622 - > 00:07:37,389
about policies without me?
没有我的政策？
00:07:38,625 - > 00:07:40,026
Um...
嗯...
00:07:56,944 - > 00:07:58,110
You're in my seat.
你坐在我的座位上。
00:08:00,713 - > 00:08:04,451
So what policies
are we discussing
today?
那么我们今天讨论的是什
么政策呢？
00:08:08,555 - > 00:08:09,557
Nobody?
没人吗？
00:08:11,391 - > 00:08:12,893
Let's see...让我们看看...
00:08:15,228 - > 00:08:17,540
"In accordance with
“依
the U.S. Green initiative,
美国绿色倡议，
00:08:17,564 - > 00:08:21,545
"Montana is leasing 7,000
acres in Powder River
County
“蒙大拿州在粉河县租了 7000 英亩地
00:08:21,569 - > 00:08:24,379
to Sun Energies."
到太阳能。"
00:08:24,403 - > 00:08:26,281
What is Sun Energies?
什么是太阳能？
00:08:26,305 - > 00:08:29,384
It's a solar farm company.
这是一家太阳能农场公司。
00:08:29,408 - > 00:08:32,154Mm. And you are?
嗯。你是？
00:08:32,178 - > 00:08:34,189
Stanley... Roberts.
斯坦利...罗伯茨。
00:08:34,213 - > 00:08:36,024
And you are?
你是？
00:08:36,048 - > 00:08:38,562
Your chief policy
advisor, Mr.
Governor.
你的首席政策顾问，州长先
生。
00:08:38,586 - > 00:08:40,830
Well, nice to fucking meet you.
很高兴见到你。
00:08:40,854 - > 00:08:43,099
I tried to schedule
我试着安排
a lunch but you're...
一顿午餐，但是你...
00:08:43,123 - > 00:08:45,125
She said you
aren't taking
lunches.
她说你不吃午饭。127
00:08:46,192 - > 00:08:48,071
Where's your office, Stanley?
你的办公室在哪里，斯坦利？
00:08:48,095 - > 00:08:50,105
Just... Right down the hall.
仅仅...就在走廊尽头。
00:08:50,129 - > 00:08:52,408
Know what? So is mine.
知道什么？我的也是。
00:08:52,432 - > 00:08:55,778
Ever dawn on you just
to come by and say
howdy?
你有没有想过过来说声你好？
00:08:55,802 - > 00:08:58,114
My mistake.
我的错误。
00:08:58,138 - > 00:08:59,615
I'd say.
我会说。133
00:08:59,639 - > 00:09:04,120
Let's see what other
policies I'm
proposing.
让我们看看我还提议了什么政
策。
00:09:04,144 - > 00:09:06,755
Suspend natural gas
leases on state
land
暂停国有土地上的天然气
租赁
00:09:06,779 - > 00:09:08,625
in Powder River
County to
support
在粉河县大力支持
00:09:08,649 - > 00:09:10,817
the Sage Grouse
Restoration Project.
塞奇松鸡修复项目。
00:09:15,788 - > 00:09:19,602
Um, there's been a
precipitous drop in sage
grouse numbers
嗯，鼠尾草松鸡的数量急剧下降
00:09:19,626 - > 00:09:21,437
and there is empirical evidence
有经验证据表明139
00:09:21,461 - > 00:09:23,673
that gas
exploration and
extraction
天然气勘探和开采
00:09:23,697 - > 00:09:27,711
have a negative impact on
the sage grouse
environment.
对鼠尾草松鸡环境有负面影响。
00:09:27,735 - > 00:09:29,612
And what effect do you
think seven thousand
acres
你认为七千英亩会有什么影响
00:09:29,636 - > 00:09:32,314
of solar panels are going
to have on their
environment?
太阳能电池板对环境的影响。
00:09:32,338 - > 00:09:35,350
There's... no
evidence that solar
panels
那有...没有证据表明太阳能
电池板144
00:09:35,375 - > 00:09:37,419
would have any impact on
会对什么有影响
the sage grouse environment.
鼠尾草松鸡环境。
00:09:37,443 - > 00:09:38,621
What do they do
with the sage
brush
他们用鼠尾草画笔做什么
00:09:38,645 - > 00:09:40,456
when they put in
the solar
panels?
当他们安装太阳能电池
板时。
00:09:40,480 - > 00:09:43,259
They, they...
他们，他们...
00:09:43,283 - > 00:09:45,794
They would clear it before
putting in the solar
panels.
他们会在安装太阳能电池板之前清理
干净。
00:09:45,818 - > 00:09:47,963
They remove the sage brush.
他们拿走了鼠尾草画笔。150
00:09:47,988 - > 00:09:50,232
Yes, sir.
是的先生。
00:09:50,256 - > 00:09:52,325
Sage grouse live
in the sage
brush.
鼠尾草松鸡生活在鼠尾
草丛中。
00:09:53,661 - > 00:09:54,903
They do.
确实如此。
00:09:54,927 - > 00:09:57,039
And you don't think
removing the sage
brush
你不认为移除鼠尾草画笔
00:09:57,063 - > 00:09:59,075
is going to have an
effect on the
population?
会对人口产生影响。
00:09:59,099 - > 00:10:01,576
I just said
我刚刚说了there's no evidence...
没有证据...
00:10:01,600 - > 00:10:03,971
Know what scares me about
you, Stanley? You're
serious.
你知道我害怕你什么吗，斯坦利？你是
认真的。
00:10:05,572 - > 00:10:07,984
You're looking at me
and you're not
joking.
你看着我，你不是在开玩笑。
00:10:08,008 - > 00:10:09,619
I think tops on my agenda today
我认为今天最重要的是
00:10:09,643 - > 00:10:13,623
is going to be budget
discipline. You're all fired.
将会是预算纪律。你们都被解雇了。
00:10:13,647 - > 00:10:15,390
I'm very mindful of
our tax payers'
money,
我非常关心纳税人的钱，
00:10:15,414 - > 00:10:17,125
and you are all wasting it.
你们都在浪费它。162
00:10:17,149 - > 00:10:19,629
I'll advise
myself on policy,
Clara.
我会给自己一些政策建
议，克拉拉。
00:10:19,653 - > 00:10:22,264
How much money did we just save?
我们刚刚省了多少钱？
00:10:22,288 - > 00:10:24,067
I would say...
我会说...
00:10:24,091 - > 00:10:26,836
Roughly 1.6 Million
大约 160 万
dollars in salary and benefits
工资和福利的美元
00:10:26,860 - > 00:10:28,270
if you're serious.
如果你是认真的。
00:10:28,294 - > 00:10:29,962Oh, I'm pretty serious.
哦，我是认真的。
00:10:33,332 - > 00:10:34,433
Look at that.
看那个。
00:10:36,369 - > 00:10:38,246
What a great day for
the State of
Montana.
对蒙大拿州来说这是多么伟
大的一天啊。
00:10:38,270 - > 00:10:40,115
Where to next?
接下来去哪里？
00:10:40,139 - > 00:10:42,818
We have an emergency
meeting with park
officials
我们和公园官员有个紧急会议
00:10:42,842 - > 00:10:44,610
and U.S. Fish and Wildlife.
美国鱼类和野生动物。
00:10:46,178 - > 00:10:47,890
Emergency meeting about what?
关于什么的紧急会议？
00:10:47,914 - > 00:10:49,424
Doesn't say.
没说。
00:10:49,448 - > 00:10:50,927
Usually means
通常意味着
someone died in the park.
有人死在公园里。
00:10:50,951 - > 00:10:52,251
They're in your office.
他们在你的办公室。
00:10:57,924 - > 00:10:59,702
What's the emergency?
有什么紧急情况？
00:10:59,726 - > 00:11:03,339
Governor, we'd like for
you to take a look at this
map.
州长，我们想让你看看这张地图。
00:11:03,363 - > 00:11:06,241
The red lines indicate the
path of a radio-collared wolf
红线表示无线电领狼的路径180
00:11:06,265 - > 00:11:09,245
associated with
the Rescue Creek
pack.
与救援队有关联。
00:11:09,269 - > 00:11:10,714
All right.
好吧。
00:11:10,738 - > 00:11:11,847
As you can see...
正如你看到的那样...
00:11:11,871 - > 00:11:13,548
Wherever we see these clusters,
无论我们在哪里看到这些星团，
00:11:13,572 - > 00:11:15,719
we associate with a kill site.
我们和一个杀人地点有关联。
00:11:15,743 - > 00:11:18,520
They'll feed on a carcass for
a few days, then they'll move
on.
它们会以尸体为食几天，然后继续前进。
00:11:18,544 - > 00:11:22,091
They left the park hereroughly three weeks
ago,
他们大约三周前离开了公园，
00:11:22,115 - > 00:11:23,960
they traveled the
tree line to
here,
他们沿着林木线来到这
里，
00:11:23,984 - > 00:11:26,485
then they dropped down
in this valley to
here.
然后他们从这个山谷掉到这
里。
00:11:28,755 - > 00:11:30,265
Mm hm.
嗯嗯。
00:11:30,289 - > 00:11:32,467
That's my ranch.
那是我的牧场。
00:11:32,491 - > 00:11:33,659
We're aware.
我们知道。192
00:11:34,995 - > 00:11:36,538
The wolves
clustered here for
three days,
狼群在这里聚集了三天，
00:11:36,562 - > 00:11:38,942
around what
围绕什么
appears to be a kill,
似乎是谋杀，
00:11:38,966 - > 00:11:42,335
then they move straight
然后他们直线前进
south for thirty miles to here.
往南三十英里到这里。
00:11:44,171 - > 00:11:45,814
Now, that's the
Yellowstone River...
这是黄石河...
00:11:45,838 - > 00:11:49,118
They jump into the
river, according to this
data
根据这个数据，他们跳进河里
00:11:49,142 - > 00:11:51,077
and they swim
他们游泳
downstream for five miles.
下游五英里。198
00:11:52,312 - > 00:11:55,457
Wasn't aware
wolves swam down
rivers.
我不知道狼会在河里游
泳。
00:11:55,481 - > 00:11:56,893
They don't.
他们没有。
00:11:56,917 - > 00:11:59,962
We recovered one of the
我们找到了其中一个
radio collars from the river.
河里的无线电项圈。
00:11:59,986 - > 00:12:01,764
What are you getting at?
你在暗示什么？
00:12:01,788 - > 00:12:03,767
We think the wolves
我们认为狼群
were killed on your
ranch 203
00:12:03,791 - > 00:12:06,225
and the collars
还有衣领
transported back to the park.
被送回公园。
00:12:10,496 - > 00:12:13,408
You think my
cowboys killed
those wolves.
你认为我的牛仔杀了那些
狼。
00:12:13,432 - > 00:12:16,036
We think your
cowboys killed those
wolves.
我们认为你的牛仔杀了那些
狼。
00:12:31,283 - > 00:12:32,528
Yes sir?
是的，先生？
00:12:32,552 - > 00:12:34,963
We had any wolves
messing with the
cattle?
有狼在骚扰牛群吗？
00:12:34,988 - > 00:12:37,365
Wolves? No sir.
狼？没有先生。
Fish and Wildlife came
鱼类和野生动物来了
by asking the same thing.
问同样的问题。
00:12:40,659 - > 00:12:41,727
All right.
好吧。
00:12:44,596 - > 00:12:46,109
There you have it.
这就是了。
00:12:46,133 - > 00:12:48,812
Look, if they
get into your
cattle
听着，如果它们进入了
你的牛群
00:12:48,836 - > 00:12:51,413
you gotta do what you gotta do.
你得做你该做的。
00:12:51,437 - > 00:12:55,350
They shot them from a
distance 215
00:12:55,375 - > 00:12:57,821
didn't notice the collar,
没注意到领子，
00:12:57,845 - > 00:13:00,355
got spooked and tried
to cover their
tracks.
受到惊吓并试图掩盖他们的踪
迹。
00:13:00,379 - > 00:13:02,958
These radio collars
aren't monitored by
us.
这些无线电项圈不受我们监
控。
00:13:02,982 - > 00:13:05,094
An NGO pays for this research,
一个非政府组织资助了这项研究，
00:13:05,118 - > 00:13:06,830
and they have
the same data we
have
他们有和我们一样的数
据
00:13:06,854 - > 00:13:09,565
and they are going to
draw the same
conclusion.
他们会得出同样的结论。
00:13:09,589 - > 00:13:11,835
When they do,
当他们这么做的时候，
00:13:11,859 - > 00:13:13,939
they will come after you
with both barrels,
Governor.
他们会带着两个桶来找你的，州长。
00:13:15,095 - > 00:13:16,495
Look forward to it.
期待吧。
00:13:17,629 - > 00:13:18,730
Anything else?
还有别的吗？
00:13:20,366 - > 00:13:22,410
Thank you, gentlemen.
Governor, we have
the...
谢谢，先生们。州长，我们
有...
00:13:22,434 - > 00:13:23,870
Yep.
没错
。
00:13:35,048 - > 00:13:37,961
Environmental groups
can be a real
problem.
环保团体可能是一个真正的问
题。
00:13:37,985 - > 00:13:40,129
Yeah, you don't say.
是啊，你没说。
00:13:45,692 - > 00:13:46,903
This is Clara.
这是克拉拉。
00:13:46,927 - > 00:13:49,538
It's Jamie, let me speak to him.
是 Jamie，让我和他说话。
00:13:49,562 - > 00:13:50,998
Attorney general.
司法部长。
00:13:52,231 - > 00:13:53,676
Yeah?
是吗？
00:13:53,700 - > 00:13:55,610
All right, there is a good
chance I can make this go
away.
好吧，我有一个很好的机会来解决这件
事。234
00:13:55,634 - > 00:14:00,349
But, in case I
can't, I need you to
know
但是，万一我不能，我需要
你知道
00:14:00,373 - > 00:14:02,585
that I'm in police
station in
Bozeman
我在波兹曼的警察局</i
>
00:14:02,609 - > 00:14:04,419
hoping to convince
a young woman to
drop
希望说服一位年轻女性放
弃
00:14:04,443 - > 00:14:06,956
the aggravated
assault charges she
plans
她计划的严重人身攻击指控
00:14:06,980 - > 00:14:08,681
to file against your
daughter. 239
00:14:11,551 - > 00:14:13,086
This fucking day.
这该死的一天。
00:14:15,187 - > 00:14:17,332
Can I, uh...
我能，呃...
00:14:17,356 - > 00:14:19,567
Can I have a little
more context,
Jamie?
Jamie，我能多讲一点上
下文吗？
00:14:19,591 - > 00:14:22,304
Yeah, she mouthed
off to Beth in a
bar
是的，她在酒吧里对贝丝
说了些什么
00:14:22,328 - > 00:14:25,240
and it went
about how you'd
expect.
就像你所期望的那样。
00:14:25,264 - > 00:14:28,500
All right. Just,
uh, keep me
posted.
好吧。有消息随时通知
我。
00:14:30,336 - > 00:14:35,484
Is there a crisis manager
on my team, by any
chance?
我的团队里有危机经理吗？
00:14:35,508 - > 00:14:39,422
Well, that would be your
press secretary who you never
hired,
嗯，那可能是你从未雇佣过的新闻秘
书，
一周七天
00:14:39,446 - > 00:14:42,548
so I guess your
crisis manager is
me.
所以我猜你的危机管理人是
我。
00:14:44,750 - > 00:14:46,461
Can I have a minute?
能给我一分钟吗？
00:14:48,087 - > 00:14:49,465
Having fun yet?
玩得开心吗？
00:14:49,489 - > 00:14:51,466
No chance you'd
你不可能
want to change jobs?
想换工作？251
00:14:51,490 - > 00:14:53,101
You'd hate this one more.
你会更讨厌这个。
00:14:54,793 - > 00:14:56,504
Any chance you're in Helena?
你有可能在海伦娜吗？
00:14:56,528 - > 00:14:58,206
A good chance.
一个好机会。
00:14:58,230 - > 00:15:01,177
- Lunch plans?
- 午餐计划？
- Not anymore.
-不再是了。
00:15:01,201 - > 00:15:03,379
- You know Benny's Bistro?
你知道本尼的小酒馆吗？
- Sure.
- 当然可以。
00:15:03,403 - > 00:15:05,614
- Noon?
- 中午？
- You made my day.
-你让我开心。
Yeah, maybe you can
是的，也许你可以
make mine. See you in a bit.
做我的。一会儿见。
00:15:22,522 - > 00:15:23,523
Yes, sir.
是的先生。
00:15:35,001 - > 00:15:36,078
Miss Brewer.
布鲁尔小姐。
00:15:36,102 - > 00:15:38,014
I understand
我明白
you'd like to press.
你想按。
00:15:38,038 - > 00:15:39,471
Very much.
非常喜欢。
00:15:44,110 - > 00:15:47,090
I feel I must
我觉得我必须
point out that by doing so,
指出这样做，263
00:15:47,114 - > 00:15:49,725
you are exposing
yourself to
prosecution.
你将面临起诉。
00:15:49,749 - > 00:15:52,695
How am I doing that?
我是怎么做到的？
00:15:52,719 - > 00:15:55,498
There is no self
defense claim in a bar
fight.
在酒吧斗殴中没有自卫的权利。
00:15:55,522 - > 00:15:58,000
I assume you had been
drinking, and I understand
you
我想你喝了酒，我理解你
00:15:58,024 - > 00:16:01,236
approached Miss Dutton
走近达顿小姐
and instigated the incident.
并煽动了这起事件。
00:16:01,260 - > 00:16:04,539
I didn't instigate anything.
我没有煽动任何事情。
00:16:04,563 - > 00:16:06,033
Oh, um...
哦，嗯...
00:16:07,734 - > 00:16:09,412
Let me see.
让我看看。
00:16:09,436 - > 00:16:12,081
Yeah, you approached
Miss Dutton and
stated,
是的，你找到达顿小姐说，
00:16:12,105 - > 00:16:15,018
"I'm taking your husband home.
“我带你丈夫回家。
00:16:15,042 - > 00:16:16,485
"You can come with us and watch
“你可以和我们一起去看
00:16:16,509 - > 00:16:19,455
or he can tell you
about it
tomorrow."
或者他可以明天告诉
你。"275
00:16:19,479 - > 00:16:21,880
Are those not your words?
这不是你的原话吗？
00:16:23,182 - > 00:16:24,226
I mean...
(解释或更正刚说过的话)我是说...
00:16:24,250 - > 00:16:26,052
I was kidding.
我开玩笑的。
00:16:27,053 - > 00:16:28,197
Mm.
嗯。
00:16:28,221 - > 00:16:30,057
She didn't find it very funny.
她不觉得这很有趣。
00:16:31,158 - > 00:16:32,158
No shit.
没错。
00:16:34,793 - > 00:16:38,173
Making statements or actions
that threaten harm to another
做出威胁伤害他人的声明或行动282
00:16:38,197 - > 00:16:42,510
or make them feel they
are in danger is
assault.
或者让他们觉得自己处于危险之
中就是侵犯。
00:16:42,534 - > 00:16:44,246
You don't have to hit
somebody to commit
assault,
你不一定要打人才算侵犯他人，
00:16:44,270 - > 00:16:46,048
you just have to
present a
threat.
你只需要提出一个威
胁。
00:16:46,072 - > 00:16:48,583
You presented the threat.
你提出了威胁。
00:16:48,607 - > 00:16:50,686
So if you press
charges 287
00:16:50,710 - > 00:16:52,421
the state must
press charges
against you.
州政府必须起诉你。
00:16:52,445 - > 00:16:54,389
And since you are not
a resident of
Montana,
因为你不是蒙大拿州的居民，
00:16:54,413 - > 00:16:58,193
you present a flight risk
你有逃跑的危险
and you bail will be withheld.
你的保释将被中止。
00:16:58,217 - > 00:17:00,528
Do you
understand what
that means?
你明白这意味着什么
吗？
00:17:00,552 - > 00:17:03,365
So she just...
所以她只是...
00:17:03,389 - > 00:17:04,766
She just gets away with it?
她就这么逃脱了吗？
She didn't get
她没有得到
away with anything.
带走任何东西。
00:17:06,358 - > 00:17:07,703
She spent the night in jail
and she's going to be charged
她在监狱里呆了一夜，她将被起诉
00:17:07,727 - > 00:17:11,273
with disorderly conduct.
行为不检。
00:17:11,298 - > 00:17:13,276
The choice is yours.
选择权在你。
00:17:15,201 - > 00:17:17,279
I can't wait to
get out of this
state.
我等不及要脱离这种状态
了。
00:17:17,304 - > 00:17:19,747
Those fucking hillbillies.
那些该死的乡巴佬。299
00:17:19,771 - > 00:17:21,449
Well, the feeling is mutual.
嗯，这种感觉是相互的。
00:17:21,473 - > 00:17:23,318
May I leave?
我可以离开吗？
00:17:23,343 - > 00:17:24,876
Please.
求你了。
00:17:30,817 - > 00:17:32,451
Saved me a ton of paperwork.
帮我省了一大堆文书工作。
00:17:33,586 - > 00:17:34,586
Thanks.
谢了。
00:17:36,989 - > 00:17:38,490
Happy to help.
乐意帮忙。
00:18:57,703 - > 00:18:58,980
What're they doing?
他们在做什么？
00:18:59,005 - > 00:19:01,039
For Kayce's boy is my guess.
我猜是为了凯斯的儿子。
00:19:27,433 - > 00:19:28,910
They told us this spot.
他们告诉我们这个地方。
00:19:28,934 - > 00:19:31,213
If I would've known I
would have dug that hole
for you.
如果我知道，我会为你挖那个洞。
00:19:31,238 - > 00:19:34,140
We don't mind. It's
part of the
ceremony.
我们不介意。这是仪式的一
部分。
00:19:34,240 - > 00:19:35,650
There's a dead horse over there.
那边有一匹死马。
00:19:35,674 - > 00:19:36,851
When did he die?
他什么时候死的？312
00:19:36,875 - > 00:19:38,320
He died Monday.
他于周一去世。
00:19:38,345 - > 00:19:40,322
I got an excavator
coming out tomorrow to
bury him.
我明天找了一辆挖掘机来埋他。
00:19:40,346 - > 00:19:41,623
We'll bury him now.
我们现在就埋葬他。
00:19:41,647 - > 00:19:43,583
We'll put him in the
ground beside the
boy.
我们会把他埋在男孩旁边。
00:19:45,617 - > 00:19:46,618
Can I ask you why?
我能问你为什么吗？
00:19:48,721 - > 00:19:51,533
You can ask, but I
ain't gonna
answer.
你可以问，但我不会回
答。
Kayce's all
right with this,
then?
那凯茜同意了吗？
00:19:53,526 - > 00:19:54,961
He knows.
他知道了。
00:19:56,262 - > 00:19:58,005
Well, you're
gonna need a big
hole.
你需要一个大洞。
00:19:58,029 - > 00:20:00,375
Jake, Ethan,
run back to the
barn
杰克，伊森，跑回谷
仓
00:20:00,400 - > 00:20:02,677
and grab us a bunch of shovels.
给我们拿几把铲子。
00:20:02,701 - > 00:20:04,604
I'll help you, Mo.
我会帮你的，莫。324
00:20:33,732 - > 00:20:35,034
Thank you.
谢谢你。
00:20:46,177 - > 00:20:47,880
Don't wish for
不要希望
what you don't want.
你不想要的。
00:20:49,816 - > 00:20:51,856
You're in it now, John.
你现在已经在里面了，约翰。
You might as well accept it.
你不妨接受它。
00:20:52,984 - > 00:20:54,296
All right.
好吧。
00:20:54,320 - > 00:20:59,801
Explain this job to me,
because it makes no
sense.
给我解释一下这个工作，因为它毫
无意义。
00:20:59,826 - > 00:21:03,571
All I do is go to middle
schools and ribbon
cuttings.
我所做的就是去中学和剪彩。
00:21:03,596 - > 00:21:05,340
Well, when the
legislature's in
session
当立法机关开会时
00:21:05,365 - > 00:21:08,343
you'll be praying
for ribbon
cuttings.
你会为剪彩而祈祷。
00:21:08,367 - > 00:21:11,446
At the end of the day,
Montana is a
business...
归根结底，蒙大拿州是一个商业
区...
00:21:11,471 - > 00:21:14,982
12,000 employees,
12000 名员工，
600,000 customers,
60 万顾客，
00:21:15,007 - > 00:21:17,619
and you're the CEO,
你是首席执行官，
and that's all there
is. 335
00:21:17,644 - > 00:21:19,053
And you really need to
change your
perspective
你真的需要改变你的视角
00:21:19,077 - > 00:21:21,122
about these
school meetings,
too.
关于这些学校会议。
00:21:21,146 - > 00:21:23,325
You know, these kids are
gonna remember meeting the
governor
你知道，这些孩子会记得见过州长
00:21:23,349 - > 00:21:24,926
for the rest of their lives.
在他们的余生中。
00:21:24,951 - > 00:21:26,361
And who knows, you
might even inspire one
of them
谁知道呢，你甚至可能会启发他
们中的一个
00:21:26,385 - > 00:21:28,029
to become the governor one day.
有朝一日成为州长。
00:21:28,054 - > 00:21:29,497I mean, that's
我是说，那是
how I was inspired.
我是如何受到启发的。
00:21:29,521 - > 00:21:31,866
All right, point taken.
好吧，明白了。
00:21:31,891 - > 00:21:34,336
I stepped on a few
land mines it
appears.
看来我踩到了几颗地雷。
00:21:34,361 - > 00:21:35,903
Already?
已经吗？
00:21:35,927 - > 00:21:37,805
Others stepped on them for me.
别人替我踩的。
00:21:37,829 - > 00:21:42,810
Seems my daughter
似乎我的女儿
got herself into a bar fight
卷入了一场酒吧斗殴347
00:21:42,835 - > 00:21:45,413
and has been arrested.
并已被逮捕。
00:21:45,438 - > 00:21:48,351
I'm sorry. It's not funny.
我很抱歉一点都不好笑。
00:21:48,375 - > 00:21:51,118
I can see how that's
funny to anybody but
me.
除了我之外，我知道这对任何人
来说有多好笑。
00:21:51,143 - > 00:21:54,155
All right, well, if it
doesn't go away, just ignore
it.
好吧，如果它不消失，就忽略它。
00:21:54,180 - > 00:21:56,358
You don't comment
你不要发表意见
on your personal family.
你个人的家庭。
00:21:56,383 - > 00:21:58,926
You love your daughter and
你爱你的女儿
hope she learns from her mistakes.
希望她能从错误中吸取教训。
00:21:58,951 - > 00:22:01,463
If she's
convicted, what
are my...
如果她被判有罪，我
的...
00:22:01,488 - > 00:22:02,864
what are my options?
我有什么选择？
00:22:02,888 - > 00:22:05,066
You have none.
你没有。
00:22:05,090 - > 00:22:07,669
Well, I take that
back, you could pardon
her,
好吧，我收回刚才的话，你可
以原谅她，
00:22:07,693 - > 00:22:11,839
but that's officially the end
of your political career,
so...
但这正式宣告了你政治生涯的终结，所
以...
00:22:11,864 - > 00:22:14,642
I don't have to wait
我不用等了until the end of my term
直到我任期结束
00:22:14,666 - > 00:22:16,010
to pardon someone?
原谅某人？
00:22:16,035 - > 00:22:17,679
I would strongly advise it
我强烈建议这样做
00:22:17,703 - > 00:22:20,415
but no, you have
the authority to
pardon,
但是不，你有权赦免，
00:22:20,440 - > 00:22:22,617
to commute
sentence, grant
clemency,
减刑，给予宽大处理，
00:22:22,642 - > 00:22:24,051
whenever you want.
你想什么时候都行。
00:22:24,076 - > 00:22:25,720
But once you open
that Pandora's
Box,
但是一旦你打开了潘多拉
盒子，365
00:22:25,744 - > 00:22:28,523
it does not close, so...
它没有关闭，所以...
00:22:28,548 - > 00:22:29,816
Next land mine?
下一个地雷？
00:22:31,817 - > 00:22:34,896
Environmental
环境的
groups relating to...
与以下内容相关的组...
00:22:34,921 - > 00:22:35,997
wolves.
狼。
00:22:36,021 - > 00:22:39,934
- Avoid them at all costs.
- 不惜一切代价避开他们。
- Yeah.
- 是啊。
00:22:39,959 - > 00:22:41,903
Buffalo and wolves were
水牛和狼the bane of my two terms.
我两届任期的祸根。
00:22:41,927 - > 00:22:43,204
They are kryptonite.
它们是氪星石。
00:22:43,229 - > 00:22:45,807
You need to stay
你需要留下来
away and try like hell
走吧，拼命尝试
00:22:45,832 - > 00:22:47,409
to avoid taking a position.
避免采取立场。
00:22:47,433 - > 00:22:50,678
And you need to get
an environmental
advisor.
你需要一个环境顾问。
00:22:50,702 - > 00:22:53,781
Not one of your rancher
buddies, an environmentalist.
不是你的农场伙伴，是环保主义者。
00:22:53,806 - > 00:22:56,684
Someone who
understands the way
that they think
理解他们思考方式的人377
00:22:56,709 - > 00:23:01,155
so they can explain to you
这样他们就能向你解释
what the hell it is they're thinking.
他们到底在想什么。
00:23:01,180 - > 00:23:03,157
Here's my best
这是我最好的
advice about this job.
关于这份工作的建议。
00:23:03,182 - > 00:23:05,560
Good governors initiate action,
好的管理者会主动采取行动，
00:23:05,585 - > 00:23:10,164
and bad governors spend
all their time
reacting.
糟糕的州长总是不停地做出反
应。
00:23:10,189 - > 00:23:13,159
There are plenty of things
to clean up besides an
airport.
除了机场，还有很多东西要清理。382
00:23:18,464 - > 00:23:20,842
You're the only man I
know who would actually
pout
你是我认识的唯一一个会噘嘴的男
人
00:23:20,866 - > 00:23:23,778
over winning the
战胜了
election that he entered.
他参加的选举。
00:23:23,803 - > 00:23:25,171
I'm not pouting.
我没有撅嘴。
00:23:26,939 - > 00:23:32,253
Skulking, maybe,
but... not
pouting.
躲起来，也许，但是...
不是撅嘴。
00:23:32,278 - > 00:23:37,115
You know, this is as much
your legacy as that
ranch.
你知道，这和那个农场一样都是你
的遗产。
00:23:39,852 - > 00:23:41,463
You're a smart woman, Lynelle.
你是个聪明的女人，Lynelle。388
00:23:41,488 - > 00:23:44,390
Oh, you're just
figuring that
out?
哦，你刚刚才发现？
00:23:44,490 - > 00:23:47,192
Just enjoy your
享受你的
lunch, John. It's on me.
午餐，约翰。我请客。
00:24:03,843 - > 00:24:05,811
Disorderly conduct?
行为不检？
00:24:07,513 - > 00:24:08,723
Way to go.
干得好。
00:24:08,748 - > 00:24:10,024
You're welcome.
不客气
00:24:10,048 - > 00:24:12,326
Now I gotta pick up
trash on the
highway
现在我得在高速公路上捡
垃圾394
00:24:12,351 - > 00:24:13,819
with all my fucking free time.
用我所有的空闲时间。
00:24:19,526 - > 00:24:20,802
Which car is yours?
哪辆车是你的？
00:24:20,826 - > 00:24:22,504
I can't take you back.
I have to go to
Helena.
我不能带你回去。我必须去海
伦娜。
00:24:22,528 - > 00:24:25,139
- Which one?
- 哪一个？
- I'm serious.
- 我是认真的。
00:24:25,163 - > 00:24:27,341
Well, how do you want
me to get home,
Jamie?
你想让我怎么回家，杰米？
00:24:27,365 - > 00:24:31,136
Huh? Want me to hike
啊？想让我去远足吗
my skirt up on the on-ramp?
我的裙子在入口坡道上？400
00:24:32,538 - > 00:24:33,778
I doubt it'd be the first time.
我怀疑这是第一次。
00:24:53,992 - > 00:24:55,369
What the fuck is that?
那他妈的是什么？
00:24:55,394 - > 00:24:56,638
What's what?
什么是什么？
00:24:56,663 - > 00:24:58,640
The baby seat. What
the fuck is that
for?
婴儿座椅。那他妈的是干什
么用的？
00:24:58,664 - > 00:24:59,731
You have a child?
你有孩子吗？
00:25:05,738 - > 00:25:07,138
Do you have a child, Jamie?
你有孩子吗，杰米？406
00:25:10,643 - > 00:25:11,844
A boy.
一个男孩。
00:25:22,288 - > 00:25:23,789
God gave you a boy?
上帝给了你一个男孩？
00:25:28,027 - > 00:25:30,696
You have my
你有我的
womb cut out of me...
我的子宫被切开了...
00:25:32,431 - > 00:25:34,500
and God gave you a boy?
上帝给了你一个男孩？
00:25:42,608 - > 00:25:43,710
Fuck you!
去你的！
00:25:47,947 - > 00:25:49,023
Beth?
贝丝。
00:25:49,048 - > 00:25:50,592
Let me guess, is
it that brood
mare
让我猜猜，是那匹母马吗
00:25:50,616 - > 00:25:52,193
of a fucking campaign manager?
一个该死的竞选经理？
00:25:52,218 - > 00:25:55,396
- Yes.
- 是的。
- I saw her coming.
- 我看见她来了。
00:25:56,623 - > 00:25:57,932
Beth.
贝丝。
00:25:57,957 - > 00:26:01,202
Come on, Beth.
来吧贝丝。
Beth, stop, stop, stop!
贝丝停下停下停下。
00:26:01,227 - > 00:26:06,307
Taking you to that clinic is
the greatest regret of my
life.
带你去那家诊所是我一生中最大的遗憾。
00:26:06,332 - > 00:26:08,843
Of all the awful
shit that you have
done
在你做过的所有糟糕的事情
中
00:26:08,867 - > 00:26:11,045
in your 45 years on this planet,
你在这个星球上的 45 年里，
00:26:11,069 - > 00:26:13,981
Jamie, that is... that
is really saying
something.
杰米，那是...这确实说明了一些
问题。
00:26:14,006 - > 00:26:15,207
What...
什么...
00:26:16,442 - > 00:26:18,176
What did you name him?
你给他起了什么名字？
00:26:20,278 - > 00:26:21,413
He's named after me.
他以我的名字命名。
00:26:25,351 - > 00:26:26,928
Of course he is!
他当然是！425
00:26:26,952 - > 00:26:28,362
That's what the
world fucking
needs.
这就是这个世界他妈的需
要的。
00:26:28,386 - > 00:26:29,463
Another fucking you.
另一个该死的你。
00:26:29,488 - > 00:26:31,156
Beth.
贝丝。
00:26:32,924 - > 00:26:34,401
Dad doesn't know about
爸爸不知道
this. Nobody knows about this.
这个。没人知道这件事。
00:26:34,425 - > 00:26:36,327
Don't worry
about me telling
him.
别担心我会告诉他。
00:26:40,666 - > 00:26:42,644I'm gonna take him from you.
我要把他从你身边带走。
00:26:42,669 - > 00:26:47,048
I'm going to rob you
of fatherhood,
Jamie.
我要剥夺你的父亲身份，杰
米。
00:26:47,073 - > 00:26:49,116
You don't deserve it.
你不配。
00:26:49,141 - > 00:26:50,742
And he deserves better than you.
他值得比你更好的人。
00:26:52,443 - > 00:26:54,289
Next time you see him,
you can kiss him
goodbye,
下次你见到他，你可以和他吻
别，
00:26:54,313 - > 00:26:57,826
because he's as good as gone.
因为他已经死了。
00:28:22,567 - > 00:28:24,036
Car trouble?
汽车故障？437
00:28:26,372 - > 00:28:29,583
Actually, I
just got out of
jail.
实际上，我刚出狱。
00:28:29,607 - > 00:28:31,386
And when they let you
当他们让你
out, they just let you out,
出去，他们让你出去，
00:28:31,410 - > 00:28:33,788
there's no, uh, no
phone call to a
friend
没有，呃，没有给朋友打电话
00:28:33,813 - > 00:28:35,456
or a bus ticket.
或者公共汽车票。
00:28:35,480 - > 00:28:38,584
Just, you know, let
you out on the
street.
只是，你知道，让你在街上。
00:28:42,421 - > 00:28:46,233Seems an unfair policy
toward one who is
clearly
似乎对一个明显
00:28:46,258 - > 00:28:50,962
having trouble coping in
society, don't you
think?
在社会上有困难，你不觉得吗？
00:28:52,131 - > 00:28:54,876
Definitely creates, uh...
绝对创造了，呃...
00:28:54,901 - > 00:28:57,578
Additional challenges for sure.
肯定会有更多的挑战。
00:28:57,603 - > 00:28:58,670
Right?
对吗？
00:29:01,272 - > 00:29:03,275
- Do you need a...
- 你需要吗...
- Ride?
- 骑马？
00:29:04,576 - > 00:29:05,978
I'd love one.
我想要一个。449
00:29:11,383 - > 00:29:12,417
Thank you.
谢谢你。
00:29:14,820 - > 00:29:16,823
What are the odds
that you have a
cigarette?
你有香烟的几率有多大？
00:29:17,522 - > 00:29:18,891
Not good.
不太好。
00:29:22,327 - > 00:29:24,438
Well, aren't you cute?
你不可爱吗？
00:29:24,462 - > 00:29:27,141
Mom's gonna kill you, Dad.
妈妈会杀了你的，爸爸。
00:29:27,165 - > 00:29:29,076
Is Mom the jealous type?
妈妈是嫉妒型的吗？455
00:29:29,101 - > 00:29:31,303
Mom wears the pants,
妈妈穿裤子，
if you know what I mean.
如果你明白我的意思。
00:29:33,305 - > 00:29:38,009
Sister, I know
exactly what you
mean.
姐姐，我完全明白你的意思。
00:30:01,067 - > 00:30:02,634
Stop the car.
停车。
00:31:12,203 - > 00:31:13,538
Nobody told me.
没人告诉我。
00:31:15,507 - > 00:31:17,242
He didn't tell anybody.
他没有告诉任何人。
00:31:18,376 - > 00:31:20,846
Just pulled up
and saw all the
cars.
刚停下来看到所有的
车。
Should we, uh, get closer?
我们应该，呃，靠近点吗？
00:31:29,587 - > 00:31:31,823
I think this is as
close as they want us,
Dad.
我想这是他们最想要的，爸爸。
00:31:42,468 - > 00:31:43,835
So how was jail?
监狱怎么样？
00:31:45,703 - > 00:31:47,181
Loud-mouthed pussy.
大嘴猫。
00:31:47,205 - > 00:31:48,683
You and I are going
你和我要去
to have a long talk later.
待会再长谈。
00:31:48,707 - > 00:31:50,284
Yeah, well, I'm
是啊，我
going to sleep later.
一会要睡觉了。467
00:31:50,308 - > 00:31:51,676
We'll have a short one now then.
那我们现在就来个简短的。
00:31:53,412 - > 00:31:54,980
Impulse control.
冲动控制。
00:31:56,982 - > 00:31:57,983
Find some.
找一些。
00:32:17,036 - > 00:32:18,569
I don't think they want us here.
我不认为他们希望我们在这里。
00:32:20,006 - > 00:32:22,984
Even if they don't want us,
即使他们不想要我们，
00:32:23,009 - > 00:32:24,875
they need to know
他们需要知道
we care enough to stay.
我们很想留下来。
00:32:28,846 - > 00:32:30,491
Make me a promise.
向我保证。474
00:32:30,516 - > 00:32:33,194
Don't ever let
永远不要让
them do that to me.
他们这样对我。
00:32:33,219 - > 00:32:35,354
Turn me to ashes and
throw me to the
wind.
把我化为灰烬，扔到风中。
00:32:36,922 - > 00:32:38,289
That's all the care I want.
这就是我想要的全部关心。
00:33:44,955 - > 00:33:46,157
John.
约翰。
00:33:47,393 - > 00:33:48,960
I'm not sure the protocol.
我不确定协议。
00:33:49,095 - > 00:33:51,673
There's no protocol now.
现在没有协议了。480
00:33:51,697 - > 00:33:53,098
Ceremony's over.
仪式结束了。
00:33:54,766 - > 00:33:56,367
I wish I'd known.
我希望我知道。
00:33:57,769 - > 00:33:59,704
Grief isn't meant to be shared.
悲伤不应该被分享。
00:34:01,539 - > 00:34:04,251
But comfort is.
但舒适才是。
00:34:04,276 - > 00:34:05,411
They could use some now.
他们现在可以用一些。
00:34:13,152 - > 00:34:14,585
John...
约翰...
00:34:16,188 - > 00:34:19,791
This isn't the place
but we do need to
talk.
这不是地方，但我们确实需要
谈谈。487
00:34:20,858 - > 00:34:22,369
About what?
关于什么？
00:34:22,393 - > 00:34:24,606
About the three
hundred jobs you
eliminated
关于你裁掉的 300 个职位
00:34:24,630 - > 00:34:28,409
when you canceled
the airport
project.
当你取消机场项目的时
候。
00:34:28,434 - > 00:34:31,278
A lot of very unhappy
people on the
Reservation.
保留地上有很多非常不开心的人。
00:34:31,302 - > 00:34:35,216
Can you meet me at
the Capitol
tomorrow?
你明天能在国会大厦见我
吗？492
00:34:35,240 - > 00:34:38,043
I think you should
meet me on the
Reservation.
我想你应该在保留区见我。
00:34:38,143 - > 00:34:40,378
Show the people you
care enough to
visit.
向你关心的人展示你的来
访。
00:34:43,849 - > 00:34:44,882
I can do that.
我能做到。
00:35:09,175 - > 00:35:10,476
I know how you feel.
我知道你的感受。
00:35:12,577 - > 00:35:16,047
I wished I didn't, but I do.
我希望我没有，但我有。
00:35:18,583 - > 00:35:22,229
I buried a son right over there.
我就在那里埋了一个儿子。
00:35:22,253 - > 00:35:23,521
I remember.我记得。
00:35:28,025 - > 00:35:29,460
Blaming yourself, aren't you?
责怪你自己，不是吗？
00:35:31,230 - > 00:35:34,233
Yeah, I did that, too.
是的，我也这么做了。
00:35:35,400 - > 00:35:37,202
Still do some days.
仍然做一些天。
00:35:39,204 - > 00:35:43,184
I'll tell you something
I've never told
anybody.
我要告诉你一些我从未告诉过任
何人的事。
00:35:43,208 - > 00:35:45,352
I had a brother for
about eighteen
hours.
我有一个哥哥大约 18 个小
时。
00:35:45,376 - > 00:35:47,655His name was Peter.
他的名字叫彼得。
00:35:47,679 - > 00:35:50,191
He was born early,
他出生很早，
00:35:50,215 - > 00:35:53,760
and his little heart
wasn't strong
enough.
他幼小的心灵不够强大。
00:35:53,784 - > 00:35:55,829
Not much they could
他们能做的不多
do back in those days.
回到那些日子。
00:35:55,853 - > 00:35:58,889
Not a lot they can do now.
他们现在能做的不多。
00:36:00,226 - > 00:36:03,405
So, they just gave
所以，他们只是给了
him back to my mother.
把他还给我妈妈。
00:36:03,429 - > 00:36:06,273
The doctors hoped
and we prayed
and...
医生希望我们祈祷...511
00:36:06,297 - > 00:36:07,632
neither worked.
两个都没用。
00:36:08,800 - > 00:36:10,777
And it changed my
mother. It hardened
her.
它改变了我的母亲。这让她变得
坚强。
00:36:10,802 - > 00:36:14,905
She never... she never
她从来没有...她从来没有
tried to have children again.
试着再要孩子。
00:36:16,242 - > 00:36:20,053
Years later, I was grown
and Lee had just been
born.
几年后，我长大了，李刚刚出生。
00:36:20,077 - > 00:36:24,226
Both my parents are looking
我父母都在找
at him, taking turns holding him.
看着他，轮流抱着他。516
00:36:24,250 - > 00:36:27,027
And my father
got white as a
ghost,
我父亲脸色变得苍白如
鬼，
00:36:27,052 - > 00:36:30,231
looked at my mother and said,
看着我妈妈说，
00:36:30,255 - > 00:36:31,922
"Peter lived a perfect life.
“彼得过着完美的生活。
00:36:33,291 - > 00:36:35,669
"All he saw of
“他看到的一切
this planet was you
这个星球就是你
00:36:35,693 - > 00:36:38,429
and all he knew
他所知道的
was you loved him."
你爱他。"
00:36:42,132 - > 00:36:43,945
That boy lived a
perfect life,
Monica.
那个男孩过着完美的生活，
莫妮卡。522
00:36:43,969 - > 00:36:46,036
We're the only ones
who know it was
brief.
我们是唯一知道那很短暂的
人。
00:36:47,273 - > 00:36:50,409
All he knew was you
他只知道你
and that you loved him.
你爱他。
00:37:01,186 - > 00:37:02,688
Thank you.
谢谢你。
00:37:37,889 - > 00:37:39,123
Named him after me.
以我的名字给他命名。
00:37:41,559 - > 00:37:42,793
I did.
我做到了。
00:37:44,329 - > 00:37:46,331
Means more than
不仅仅意味着
you'll ever know, son.
你永远不会知道，儿子。528
00:37:48,967 - > 00:37:50,001
I know what it means.
我知道这意味着什么。
00:37:54,773 - > 00:37:55,806
Yeah.
是啊。
00:37:57,909 - > 00:38:00,053
Hang on to this.
抓住这个。
00:38:00,077 - > 00:38:01,488
Even if you don't use it,
即使你不用它，
00:38:01,512 - > 00:38:05,351
now is not the time to
stop drawing a
paycheck.
现在不是停止领薪水的时候。
00:38:09,119 - > 00:38:11,432
I'll find someone
to take your
place
我会找人代替你的
00:38:11,456 - > 00:38:12,990
if that's what you want.如果这是你想要的。
00:38:15,626 - > 00:38:17,094
It's what I want.
这是我想要的。
00:38:43,521 - > 00:38:45,523
Looks like you
看起来像你
got tossed off one.
被扔出一个。
00:38:46,525 - > 00:38:49,370
Just been digging graves.
只是在挖坟墓。
00:38:49,394 - > 00:38:52,262
Horses go in the
field, you know
that.
你知道，马在田野里跑。
00:38:52,398 - > 00:38:54,876
Yeah, I know but they
wanted it beside the
boy.
是的，我知道，但是他们想把它
放在男孩旁边。540
00:38:54,900 - > 00:38:56,166
Didn't figure you'd say no.
没想到你会拒绝。
00:38:58,503 - > 00:38:59,737
They say why?
他们说为什么了吗？
00:39:01,206 - > 00:39:04,775
My guess is the boy has
something to ride into
Heaven.
我猜这个男孩有东西可以骑着去天堂。
00:39:08,012 - > 00:39:09,791
Uh, the Poison Creek
outfit, they reached
out,
呃，毒溪组织，他们联系了，
00:39:09,815 - > 00:39:11,392
they're short handed to brand.
他们缺少布兰德。
00:39:11,416 - > 00:39:14,695
They wanted our help
他们需要我们的帮助
so, if you're all right with it,
所以，如果你没问题的话，
00:39:14,719 - > 00:39:15,697go over there tomorrow.
明天去那边。
00:39:15,721 - > 00:39:18,064
When are we starting?
我们什么时候开始？
00:39:18,088 - > 00:39:19,601
Well, next week.
好吧，下周。
00:39:19,625 - > 00:39:21,068
You plan on
being here,
don't you?
你打算待在这里，是
吗？
00:39:21,092 - > 00:39:23,070
I mean, it's not my place to...
我是说，这不是我该做的...
00:39:23,094 - > 00:39:25,963
- I'll be here.
- 我会在这里。
- All
right.
- 好吧。
00:39:29,867 - > 00:39:32,447
Park Rangers came and asked me
公园管理员过来问我
00:39:32,471 - > 00:39:35,449
some question about
wolves that held up
here.
这里有一些关于狼的问题。
00:39:35,474 - > 00:39:38,485
You know anything about that?
你知道些什么吗？
00:39:38,510 - > 00:39:42,122
Mm. They pulled down a cow,
嗯。他们放倒了一头牛，
00:39:42,146 - > 00:39:44,791
and I asked Ryan to
go out and shoot
'em.
我让 Ryan 出去射杀他们。
00:39:44,815 - > 00:39:47,861
He shot the ones with
the damn collars on
'em.
他杀了那些戴着该死项圈的人。
00:39:47,885 - > 00:39:51,532
I was worried that it was
going to cause you a
problem我担心这会给你带来麻烦
00:39:51,556 - > 00:39:54,901
so I tried to outsmart
'em and I guess I
didn't.
所以我试着比他们聪明，但我想
我没有。
00:39:54,925 - > 00:39:57,204
So, I'm sorry, sir.
所以，很抱歉，先生。
00:39:57,228 - > 00:39:59,206
Where are the wolves now?
狼群现在在哪里？
00:39:59,230 - > 00:40:01,467
In a place that
nobody will ever find
them.
在一个没人能找到他们的地
方。
00:40:11,842 - > 00:40:14,521
Horses in
heaven. 564
00:40:14,545 - > 00:40:16,623
Mm-hm. That's the
嗯嗯。那是
best I could figure it.
我已经尽力了。
00:40:20,952 - > 00:40:22,052
Wouldn't that be something?
那不是很了不起吗？
00:40:49,748 - > 00:40:55,253
♪ Well, in you ♪
嗯，在你身上
00:40:58,123 - > 00:41:01,869
♪ The good I'll
do Good I'll do,
oh ♪
我会做好事，我会做好
事，哦
00:41:01,893 - > 00:41:03,594
♪ The good I'll do ♪
#我会做的好事#
00:41:21,847 - > 00:41:23,657
♪ The way the
grass smells At
night ♪
#夜晚青草的味道#
00:41:23,681 - > 00:41:26,092
♪ And you've got#你得到了#
flames All in your eyes ♪
你眼中的火焰
00:41:26,117 - > 00:41:28,128
♪ As they reflect the sparkler ♪
当它们反射火花时
00:41:28,152 - > 00:41:30,264
♪ And you say we'll never die ♪
你说我们永远不会死
00:41:30,288 - > 00:41:33,767
♪ Grab me by the hands
Just as callused as I am
♪ 抓
住我的手，就像我老茧一样
00:41:33,791 - > 00:41:35,393
♪ Say your proud ♪
#说出你的骄傲#
00:41:37,862 - > 00:41:39,773
♪ Well, there's blue
jeans in the driveway
♪ 嗯
，车道上有蓝色牛仔裤
00:41:39,797 - > 00:41:41,943
♪ And you're
walking Inside
sideways ♪
#你横着走进去#
00:41:41,967 - > 00:41:46,146
♪ The wine always affects
you In beautiful kind ways
♪
？酒总是以美好的方式影响你
00:41:46,170 - > 00:41:49,349
♪ Ask me if I'm
staying And I say that
I'm ♪
问我是否会留下，我说我会
00:41:49,373 - > 00:41:50,976
♪ Sleeping on the floor ♪
#睡在地板上#
00:41:53,945 - > 00:41:56,023
♪ Won't you tell
me that you need
me ♪
你会告诉我你需要我吗
00:41:56,047 - > 00:41:59,960
♪ 'Cause lately I've been
Needing someone to remind me
♪ 因
为最近我需要有人提醒我
♪ I'm worth more
？我更有价值
than Just an evening ♪
不仅仅是一个晚上
00:42:02,588 - > 00:42:05,032
♪ I awoke to
kitchen smoke, You
dancin' ♪
§我在厨房的烟雾中醒
来，你在跳舞§
00:42:05,056 - > 00:42:07,192
♪ Like God's
moved In you
before ♪
#就像上帝之前感动了你
#
00:42:09,994 - > 00:42:14,932
♪ Well, in you ♪
嗯，在你身上
00:42:18,436 - > 00:42:22,472
♪ The good I'll
do Good I'll do,
oh ♪
我会做好事，我会做好
事，哦
00:42:22,608 - > 00:42:24,943♪ Good I'll do ♪
好，我会做的
00:42:26,510 - > 00:42:31,750
♪ Well, in you ♪
嗯，在你身上
00:42:34,619 - > 00:42:40,525
♪ I'm new, I'm
new Oh, how I'm
new ♪
我是新的，我是新的
哦，我是新的
00:42:59,710 - > 00:43:01,121
♪ Look in my eyes ♪
看着我的眼睛
00:43:01,146 - > 00:43:02,956
♪ I don't wanna to hide ♪
#我不想隐藏#
00:43:02,981 - > 00:43:04,858
♪ I've been waiting
#我一直在等待#
for you All damn night ♪
为你度过该死的一夜
00:43:04,882 - > 00:43:07,360
I know but he's
gotta go
somewhere.
我知道，但他必须去某个
地方。594
00:43:07,385 - > 00:43:11,164
♪ Sundress, I'll undress
With nails on your skin
♪ ？
太阳裙，我会脱下你皮肤上的
指甲
00:43:11,188 - > 00:43:12,456
♪ Turning white ♪
#变白#
00:43:15,326 - > 00:43:19,305
♪ Getting high out in
Austin Drunk in Tennessee
♪ 在
田纳西的奥斯汀喝醉了
00:43:19,329 - > 00:43:23,476
♪ I don't care where I am
As long as you're with me
♪
只要你和我在一起，我不在乎我在
哪里
00:43:23,501 - > 00:43:28,215
♪ Those boys downtown talk
So much shit when I leave
♪ 当
我离开时，市中心的那些男孩说
了那么多废话
00:43:28,239 - > 00:43:29,407
Good job, Reese.
干得好，里斯。
00:43:31,409 - > 00:43:35,146
♪ Well, in you ♪
嗯，在你身上
00:43:39,449 - > 00:43:43,664
♪ The good I'll
do Good I'll do,
oh ♪
我会做好事，我会做好
事，哦
00:43:43,688 - > 00:43:45,356
♪ The good I'll do ♪
#我会做的好事#
00:43:47,358 - > 00:43:52,898
♪ 'Cause in you ♪
因为在你身上
00:43:55,733 - > 00:44:01,706
♪ I'm new, I'm
new Oh, how I'm
new ♪
我是新的，我是新的
哦，我是新的
00:44:04,342 - > 00:44:06,152
♪ The way the
grass smells Atnight ♪
#夜晚青草的味道#
00:44:06,177 - > 00:44:08,612
♪ And you've got
#你得到了#
flames All in your eyes ♪
你眼中的火焰
00:44:08,713 - > 00:44:10,691
♪ As they reflect
the sparkler ♪ -
Whoo!
？因为他们反映了火花！
00:44:10,715 - > 00:44:12,959
♪ And you say we'll never die ♪
你说我们永远不会死
00:44:12,983 - > 00:44:16,329
♪ Grab me by the hands
Just as callused as I am
♪ 抓
住我的手，就像我老茧一样
00:44:16,353 - > 00:44:18,255
♪ Say your proud ♪
#说出你的骄傲#
00:44:20,257 - > 00:44:23,594
So how many
那么有多少
are y'all running this year?
你们今年会参加竞选吗？
00:44:23,728 - > 00:44:25,596
Bout the same as last year.
和去年差不多。
00:44:25,731 - > 00:44:28,742
But we won't add any
yearlings this year
though.
但是今年我们不会增加任何一岁
的。
00:44:28,766 - > 00:44:31,713
Not with diesel prices and corn.
不是柴油价格和玉米。
00:44:31,737 - > 00:44:34,247
- No.
- 号码
- Shit.
- 妈的。
00:44:34,271 - > 00:44:36,606
When this finally
makes it to the
butcher shop,
当它最终到达肉店时，
it's gonna sting.
会很疼的。
00:44:40,978 - > 00:44:42,646
It's good to see your boy back.
很高兴看到你儿子回来了。
00:44:44,414 - > 00:44:46,526
It's just for the summer.
只是为了这个夏天。
00:44:46,550 - > 00:44:51,097
He graduated,
他毕业了，
got a job in Boise.
在博伊西找了份工作。
00:44:51,121 - > 00:44:53,735
But my daughter wants to stay.
但是我女儿想留下来。
00:44:53,759 - > 00:44:55,535
We'll see if I can
make a cowboy out of
her
我们看看我能不能把她变成牛
仔
00:44:55,559 - > 00:44:58,572
shit-for-brains husband.
愚蠢的丈夫。
00:44:58,596 - > 00:45:00,907
Only thing he seems
他唯一看起来
to like making is babies.
喜欢生孩子。
00:45:00,931 - > 00:45:02,367
Is that right?
是这样吗？
00:45:03,634 - > 00:45:07,981
World sure is
世界的确如此
shrinking where you are.
在你所在的地方收缩。
00:45:08,005 - > 00:45:10,516
It's good to see
that airport
squashed.
很高兴看到机场被压扁了。
00:45:10,541 - > 00:45:13,119
That ain't gonna
那不会
change nothing, Delbert.
什么也改变不了，德尔波特。
00:45:13,143 - > 00:45:16,757I mean, shit, it
might slow it down a
bit.
我是说，妈的，可能会慢一
点。
00:45:16,782 - > 00:45:19,684
At least the world hasn't
found out about this place
yet.
至少这个世界还没发现这个地方。
00:45:21,786 - > 00:45:24,588
It breaks my heart to think
of the world we're leaving
them.
想到我们将要留给他们的世界，我的心
都碎了。
00:45:26,324 - > 00:45:27,525
Breaks my heart, too.
我也很伤心。
00:45:29,360 - > 00:45:30,996
Hell, I don't
even have any
kids.
见鬼，我甚至没有孩
子。
00:45:57,088 - > 00:45:58,722
Higgins.
希金斯。635
00:46:45,070 - > 00:46:47,248
What took you so long?
你怎么花了这么长时间？
00:46:48,338 - > 00:46:50,041
I've only been Governor a week.
我当州长才一周。
00:46:52,210 - > 00:46:53,710
I see you survived.
我看到你活下来了。
00:46:54,880 - > 00:46:57,590
- Thank you.
- 谢谢你。
- Well, there's a catch.
- 嗯，有一个条件。
00:46:57,614 - > 00:46:59,360
A catch?
一个陷阱？
00:46:59,384 - > 00:47:01,327
Yeah, it's a
supervised release for
six months.
是的，这是六个月的监管释
放。
00:47:01,351 - > 00:47:03,454Supervised by who?
受谁监督？
00:47:04,554 - > 00:47:05,556
You're looking at him.
你正看着他。
00:47:07,057 - > 00:47:10,303
So, you release me from
prison just to kidnap
me?
你把我从监狱放出来就是为了绑
架我？
00:47:10,327 - > 00:47:13,706
More or less. Need your help.
或多或少。需要你的帮助。
00:47:13,731 - > 00:47:15,541
With what?
用什么？
00:47:15,565 - > 00:47:17,378
Help me understand you.
帮我理解你。
00:47:17,402 - > 00:47:20,447Help me
understand the
way you think.
帮我理解你的思维方
式。
00:47:20,471 - > 00:47:22,483
What do I get in return?
我能得到什么回报？
00:47:22,507 - > 00:47:25,085
You just got it. Get in.
你刚刚得到它。上车吧。
00:47:25,110 - > 00:47:27,521
- Where am I staying?
- 我住在哪里？
- With me.
- 和我一起。
00:47:28,713 - > 00:47:30,323
I'm no political strategist
我不是政治战略家
00:47:30,347 - > 00:47:32,693
but granting clemency to a
woman you're shacking up with
但是宽恕一个和你同居的女人
00:47:32,717 - > 00:47:35,428
in the Governor's mansion
在州长官邸
lends itself to some negative press.
会招致一些负面报道。654
00:47:35,452 - > 00:47:36,898
At the ranch.
在牧场。
00:47:36,922 - > 00:47:39,900
Oh, great. With your
哦，太好了。用你的
bi-polar sociopathic daughter?
两极反社会的女儿？
00:47:39,925 - > 00:47:41,525
She's hardly ever there.
她几乎不在那里。
00:47:46,563 - > 00:47:49,642
So you know, I just
所以你知道，我只是
went a year without sex,
一年没有性生活，
00:47:49,666 - > 00:47:52,245
which is the longest I've
哪一个是我见过最长的
gone since the first time I had
it, 659
00:47:52,269 - > 00:47:54,547
and I'm still not fucking you.
我还是没和你上床。
00:47:54,572 - > 00:47:57,650
Oh, God.
哦，天啊。
00:47:57,675 - > 00:48:00,244
Our relationship will
be purely
professional.
我们的关系将是纯粹的职业关
系。
00:48:06,083 - > 00:48:07,585
Let her in.
让她进来。
00:48:27,371 - > 00:48:28,748
Miss Atwood.
阿特伍德小姐。
00:48:28,773 - > 00:48:31,617
Oh, come on. It's
Sarah. Have a
seat.
哦，别这样。是莎拉。请
坐。
00:48:31,641 - > 00:48:34,120
I took the liberty of
ordering us a bottle ofRosé.
我自作主张点了一瓶桃红葡萄酒。
00:48:34,144 - > 00:48:37,090
I hope you don't mind.
我希望你不介意。
00:48:37,114 - > 00:48:39,960
Well, can't say
I've ever had
it.
嗯，不能说我曾经有
过。
00:48:39,985 - > 00:48:42,695
Oh. Well the French,
哦。法国人，
00:48:42,719 - > 00:48:45,255
they drink it like
water in the
summer.
他们在夏天像喝水一样喝
它。
00:48:49,827 - > 00:48:51,161
Try it.
试试看。
00:48:59,003 - > 00:49:00,304It's refreshing.
令人耳目一新。
00:49:04,474 - > 00:49:05,909
It's nice.
挺好的。
00:49:10,248 - > 00:49:11,882
What?
什么？
00:49:12,016 - > 00:49:16,162
Oh, I'm just trying to decide
哦，我只是想决定
00:49:16,186 - > 00:49:18,498
the best path forward.
最好的前进道路。
00:49:18,523 - > 00:49:20,633
How do we manage this?
我们如何做到这一点？
00:49:20,657 - > 00:49:23,403
How do we as a company, recover?
作为一家公司，我们如何恢复？
00:49:23,427 - > 00:49:25,472
How do we save face?
我们如何挽回面子？679
00:49:25,496 - > 00:49:27,840
But most importantly, how
do we reverse his
decision?
但最重要的是，我们如何扭转他的
决定？
00:49:27,864 - > 00:49:30,643
Either reverse his
decision or get our money
back.
要么推翻他的决定，要么拿回我们
的钱。
00:49:30,668 - > 00:49:32,812
I mean, the state is facing
我是说，政府正面临着
a multi-billion dollar lawsuit
数十亿美元的诉讼
00:49:32,836 - > 00:49:34,314
and you know it.
你知道的。
00:49:34,338 - > 00:49:36,182
You won't
win.
你不会赢的。
00:49:36,206 - > 00:49:38,151
With some of the
most vital
elements
一些最重要的元素
00:49:38,175 - > 00:49:40,686
of your development now
你现在的发展
in a Conservation Easement,
在保护地役权中，
00:49:40,710 - > 00:49:42,246
the argument is moot.
这个论点没有实际意义。
00:49:44,514 - > 00:49:46,251
We don't have to win.
我们不一定要赢。
00:49:47,784 - > 00:49:51,032
We just need to
我们只需要
keep it in the news long enough
让它在新闻中出现足够长的时间
00:49:51,056 - > 00:49:53,367
to assassinate
your father's
reputation
来破坏你父亲的名誉
00:49:53,391 - > 00:49:56,793and choose a politician to
support as the next governor.
选择一位政治家作为下一任州长。
00:49:58,829 - > 00:50:00,164
Hm.
嗯。
00:50:01,498 - > 00:50:04,001
I'm getting ahead of myself.
我超越了自己。
00:50:06,204 - > 00:50:10,016
The purpose of this dinner
was to seek a soft
landing.
这次聚餐的目的是寻求软着陆。
00:50:10,041 - > 00:50:12,177
Not to threaten positions.
不要威胁立场。
00:50:14,978 - > 00:50:17,824
Let's figure out if we
can even get along
first.
先想想我们能不能相处好。696
00:50:21,018 - > 00:50:22,952
Are you hungry?
你饿了吗？
00:50:24,688 - > 00:50:26,266
Not really.
不完全是。
00:50:26,291 - > 00:50:27,867
Mm-mm. Me neither.
嗯。我也是。
00:50:27,891 - > 00:50:30,303
I've had enough
我已经受够了
of this fruity shit.
这种水果屎。
00:50:30,327 - > 00:50:33,706
[deep breath
深呼吸
00:50:33,731 - > 00:50:36,400
Do you want to go to the bar?
你想去酒吧吗？
00:50:40,170 - > 00:50:41,347
Sure.
当然可以。703
00:50:41,371 - > 00:50:43,083
Oh, that's not funny.
哦，这不好笑。
00:50:43,108 - > 00:50:47,019
Then why are you laughing?
那你为什么笑？
00:50:47,043 - > 00:50:49,422
I'm laughing
because I'm
uncomfortable.
我笑是因为我不舒服。
00:50:49,447 - > 00:50:51,815
You're uncomfortable
because you find it
funny.
你不舒服是因为你觉得好笑。
00:50:56,853 - > 00:50:59,199
I'm dreading
arguing with you in
court.
我害怕在法庭上和你争
论。
00:50:59,224 - > 00:51:01,434You should. You should.
你应该。你应该。
00:51:01,458 - > 00:51:03,128
Yeah?
是吗？
00:51:06,030 - > 00:51:08,233
How the hell are
you still
single?
你怎么还单身？
00:51:12,302 - > 00:51:15,815
Well...
良好的...
00:51:15,840 - > 00:51:20,153
when you live on a
当你生活在一个
ranch an hour from town...
离镇上一小时路程的牧场...
00:51:20,177 - > 00:51:23,523
an hour from anything...
离任何地方都有一个小时...
00:51:23,547 - > 00:51:25,949
You don't live
on a ranch
anymore.
你不再住在农场了。715
00:51:28,318 - > 00:51:32,389
Hm. No, I don't.
嗯。不，我没有。
00:51:34,958 - > 00:51:39,463
I'm feeling a
我感觉
little irresponsible.
有点不负责任。
00:51:41,666 - > 00:51:42,666
Hm.
嗯。
00:51:46,204 - > 00:51:49,615
I'm starting to feel
that way myself,
too.
我自己也开始有这种感觉
了。
00:51:49,639 - > 00:51:51,318
Oh.
哦。
00:51:51,342 - > 00:51:53,378
Take me somewhere and prove it.
带我去个地方证明一下。721
00:51:56,181 - > 00:52:00,393
♪ But you know
I've always been
♪ #
但你知道我一直都是#
00:52:00,418 - > 00:52:02,018
Follow me.
跟我来。
00:52:17,501 - > 00:52:20,070
Okay. I don't hear anybody.
好吧。我没听到任何人。
00:52:20,204 - > 00:52:21,206
Wow.
哇哦。
00:52:23,641 - > 00:52:25,242
This way.
这边走。
00:52:26,376 - > 00:52:27,987
- You...
- 你们...
- No.
- 号码
00:52:30,215 - > 00:52:32,849
This is what Icall a fucking
bathroom.
这就是我所说的他妈的浴
室。
00:53:03,947 - > 00:53:05,325
Wait. Wait...
等等。等待...
00:53:05,349 - > 00:53:08,117
Who cares? Let him listen.
谁在乎呢。让他听。
00:54:30,199 - > 00:54:31,568
What are you doing?
你在做什么?
00:54:32,670 - > 00:54:34,838
Nothing, baby. Just thinking.
没什么，宝贝。只是在想。
00:54:36,641 - > 00:54:38,561
Maybe you should think
about something
different.
也许你应该考虑一些不同的东西。
00:54:40,378 - > 00:54:45,215
I'd love to. But...
it ain't gonna
happen.
我很乐意。但是...不会发生
的。
00:54:46,550 - > 00:54:47,684
Go back to sleep.
回去睡觉吧。
00:54:59,929 - > 00:55:01,264
Who is this bitch?
这个婊子是谁？
00:55:12,009 - > 00:55:14,454
Yeah, not her real name.
是的，不是她的真名。
00:55:14,478 - > 00:55:15,545
What a surprise.
真是个惊喜。
00:55:52,717 - > 00:55:56,829
Our Justice system is in a
state of utter collapse, huh?
我们的司法系统完全崩溃了，是吧？
00:55:56,853 - > 00:56:00,867
And to think of all the hard
work I did to put you in
prison.
想想我为了把你送进监狱做了多少努力。740
00:56:00,891 - > 00:56:05,405
And think of all the hard
work I'm doing to stay
out.
想想我为了出去做了多少努力。
00:56:05,429 - > 00:56:07,139
And I do mean hard.
我是说努力。
00:56:07,164 - > 00:56:10,476
I'll pick you up some
Doxycycline when I'm in
town
我进城的时候会给你带些强力霉素
00:56:10,501 - > 00:56:13,213
to kill whatever funk your
snatch caught in the
clink.
杀了你在监狱里抓到的任何人。
00:56:13,237 - > 00:56:17,050
Mm. Thanks. Could you
also get me a
toothbrush?
嗯。谢谢。你能给我一把牙刷
吗？745
00:56:17,074 - > 00:56:19,585
I hate to keep using yours.
我讨厌一直用你的。
00:56:19,610 - > 00:56:21,110
Oh, well. Back to work.
哦，好吧。回去工作。
00:56:25,882 - > 00:56:27,518
I am not
starting this
day sober.
我不会清醒地开始新的
一天。
00:57:27,143 - > 00:57:29,045
Next time on Yellowstone...
下一集黄石公园...
00:57:30,246 - > 00:57:32,191
First Duttons
第一顿
to settle this valley...
在这个山谷定居...
00:57:32,215 - > 00:57:33,494
fighting was all they knew.
他们只知道打架。
00:57:33,518 - > 00:57:35,495
She is not gonna help you, Dad.她不会帮你的，爸爸。
00:57:35,519 - > 00:57:38,998
You have invited your
worst enemy to sleep in
your bed.
你邀请了你最大的敌人睡在你的床
上。
00:57:39,023 - > 00:57:41,101
Market Equities or its partners.
市场股票或其合作伙伴。
00:57:41,125 - > 00:57:43,268
We can do whatever we want.
我们可以为所欲为。
00:57:43,293 - > 00:57:44,537
They want the land, Dad.
他们想要土地，爸爸。
00:57:44,561 - > 00:57:46,706
That is all that
you need to
understand.
这就是你需要理解的全
部。
00:57:46,731 - > 00:57:48,908Cowards rule the
懦夫统治世界
world these days, Rip.
这个世界，李伯。
00:57:48,932 - > 00:57:51,333
I think it's time we showed
them what we do and how we do
it.
我想是时候让他们看看我们在做什么以及
我们是如何做的了。